As you already know,
你已经知道
transaction costs are a hugely important thing to think about.
交易成本是很重要的考虑因素
Can you do anything to mitigate transaction costs and the optimization problem itself?
能否在优化问题本身中减少交易成本呢？
Well, you know you want to minimize transaction costs.
我们知道我们想要最小化交易成本
Can you just plop some quantity that measures
有没有什么量可以衡量交易成本
transaction costs somehow into the objective function?
并将此量添加到目标函数中？
That sounds like a seemingly satisfying solution.
听起来似乎是很令人满意的解决方案
The problem with this is that in practice,
问题在于 在实践中
it's extremely difficult to know how to represent those costs.
很难知道如何表示交易成本
To know the transaction costs,
要知道交易成本
you must know what the trade is,
必须知道交易是什么
but the whole reason to do the optimization is to know what the traders.
但是优化的目的就是要知道交易是什么
In general, transaction cost is a function of trade size.
通常 交易成本是交易规模的函数
But the problem is even an infinitesimally small trade
但问题是 即使很小的交易
will incur non-trivial transaction costs.
也会导致很高的交易成本
That is, transaction cost is a discontinuous function of trade size.
交易成本是交易规模的不连续函数
This is because there are lower bounds on bid ask spreads and Trade Commission's.
因为买卖价差和交易佣金的限制很少
This means that a transaction cost term can't
所以我们无法轻松地
be included in the objective function easily.
将交易成本项添加到目标函数中
One possibility is to impose a turnover constraint.
一种可能是施加周转率约束条件
Again, simply limiting the net change in weight
直接对每个资产的权重相对于
on each asset relative to the weights in the previous portfolio.
上一个投资组合的权重之间的净变化进行限制
In general, turnover is directly proportional to transaction cost.
通常 周转率直接与交易成本成比例
So, you might limit turnover to say 20 percent.
例如 可以将周转率上限设为 20%
The problem with doing this is you can easily get to an infeasible situation.
这么做很容易使问题无解
It's very possible that you can have a situation where through market movements,
很有可能出现的状况是随着市场的变化
the portfolio gets pushed into a certain scenario
导致投资组合进入一种状态
where to have all the constraints satisfied,
要满足所有的约束条件
the turnover constraint must be violated.
必须违反周转率约束条件
For example, market movements may have pushed the size of
例如 市场变化可能导致股票的头寸大小
a stock's position beyond the maximum allowed by the individual weight constraint,
超过单个权重约束条件允许的最大值
but the trade required to reduce that weight
但是降低该权重所需的交易
may be more than allowed by the turnover constraint.
可能超出了周转率约束条件允许的量
There are two potential solutions.
有两种可能的解决方案
The first is to put that turnover constraint into
第一种是将周转率约束条件
a penalty term in the objective function so that instead of a hard cap,
变成目标函数的惩罚项
you have a scaling term that penalizes turnover.
这样周转率就不是硬性上限 变成惩罚周转率的调整项
The second solution is to put the whole optimization problem inside a loop.
第二种是将整个优化问题放入循环语句中
You can impose a hard turnover constraint,
可以设定硬性周转率约束条件
and if the problem is infeasible,
如果问题变得无解
you can progressively relax the turnover constraint
可以逐渐放宽周转率约束条件
and rerun the optimization until the problem becomes feasible.
并重新运行优化问题 直到问题变得有解